e e
all right uh greetings
everyone uh welcome
to
Freestyle
Wednesday um y'all go ahead and put a
one in the chat if you could hear
me and if you can see me
all right
uh what's up what's
up uh can y'all see
me you can hear me can you see
me all right
all right very good very good very good
um so welcome again everyone um I know
that we have been gone for some time um
it's actually been several months that
we have not done a
freestyle
Wednesday um but uh we are uh we are
starting this up
again so um you know we have had a a a
lot go on over the last uh several
months uh that have just uh kind of
diverted our attention to to to other
things to other issues family
issues um health issues uh particularly
with my brother um also with my wife's
brother my
brother-in-law um so it's kind of been
it's it's been a very hectic last
several
months um
but uh we're starting this up again we
are back put a one in the chat if you
are
excited um I have missed you all I have
missed our
freestyles um and uh I I look forward to
us getting into studying the word of God
together
again um so uh let me um let me start by
just kind of
um filling you all in um on on what
freestyle Wednesday is about okay uh
basically freestyle Wednesday is our uh
it is uh photo theology in action it is
photo theology in action by the way um
make sure you if you're not subscribed
to the channel make sure you subscribe
hit the share button so that you can let
others know that this is going on right
now that we are going to Freestyle
tonight um but freestyle Wednesday is
where we we basically study the Bible uh
sometimes I'll have a guest sometimes
it'll be me alone and it'll be you and I
studying uh um and that's what we're
going to do tonight tonight is going to
be us that means me and you the
audience um and we're going to Freestyle
tonight um what is photo theology photo
theology is the um it is an approach to
Bible study in which we study the Bible
through the use of images it is a study
of the word of God by comparing images
in the scriptures and so the whole
Foundation of photo theology is is how
do I translate the Bible into images
into into pictures and then compare
those pictures
um in the photo theology uh system there
are seven
floors and uh each floor has several
rooms and each room represents a
principal and so what we do in photo
theology is we'll drop a text into the
system and in dropping that text into
the system we can then move that text to
any one of over 30 rooms we've added
more rooms since we last met
but we move the text we can move the
text through 30 30 plus different rooms
and in each one of those rooms um there
are subsections to the principles that
are that are uh Amplified in that
particular room so basically what that
means beloved is you can take one text
and
find so much in that text by moving them
through the different rooms and as
you're moving them through the different
rooms and applying the different
principles to them and you find
something that becomes a brand new
thought you can take that brand new
thought and move it again through 30
plus rooms and so the cycle is really
kind of like never ending right and
that's a beautiful thing about photo
theology
so
um we we we use Photo theology cards if
you are interested in getting the cards
you see the cards on the screen behind
me but uh we have the B the photo
theology system basically uh in the form
of playing cards they're Bible study
cards and uh if you're interested in
getting those cards uh just go to photo
theology gamed deck.com let me see if I
can put that uh in the link for you
uh photo theology game
deck
do um
and that is
where uh you can get access to the
cards um so let me let me let me fill
you in on something that I think is
pretty neat um since the last time we
have spoken uh since last time we were
on together uh I am now teaching a
class um a high school class a high
school class I'm teaching them the
principles of photo theology
and uh it is beautiful to to see these
students my
students grasping this principle of
photo theology so today in class um I I
introduced them to uh what I now call
the cooking room and that's what we're
going to do tonight by the way um and so
they're like well Pastor what's the
cooking room and I said basically I'm
going to give
you uh ingredients so I have about 11 12
students in the class and so each one of
them had to take an ingredient now what
do you think I mean by ingredient let's
see if we can y'all put it in the chat
what do you think I mean by ingredient
everyone had an ingredient and together
we were going to cook up a
meal so what do you think I'm talking
about when I say everyone had an
ingredient I'm checking in the chat
everybody had an
ingredient all right well let me help
you an ingredient is a text from the
Bible remember the Bible is the word of
God we're invited to eat the word of God
the word of God is a meal yes Marco you
got it a verse so I handed out a verse
to each one of my students and um um
these are randomly chosen
verses and and so my first student went
and he had to look at his verse break
down the verse and just amplify it not a
whole lot but just amplify it and set
the foundation for the rest of the study
and then each student could then take
their hey I I can add my verse to that I
got something I found a connection
between the verse that I have and what
was just shared and so they had to take
the verse that they had and connect Ed
with the verse that was just
shared to to to to bring both the
thought in both verses together and each
student as we went on each student had
to build upon the
ingredients that the students before
them had had um had expounded
upon and so by the end of our study time
in our
classroom um it was a beautiful
study that was put together by these
students and it was pretty powerful it
was pretty
powerful um this is a technique that you
could use and you know if you're having
uh you know a youth group or something
and you're trying to find a a a creative
way to get them engaged in studying the
Bible this is a good practice this is a
good technique because everybody is
cooking together together everybody's
cooking together everybody is putting in
an ingredient to make up the meal and
everybody gets a chance to participate
in adding to the meal right in making
the meal taste even better so that's the
goal to the cooking room and tonight you
guys we're going to uh we're going to do
that um we're going to cook tonight
we're going to cook together now this is
a little bit similar to what we have
been doing with the conect six room so
remember in the connect six room what we
were doing for some time is we would
invite our guests on and then we would
allow you guys to choose something from
six different sections history prophecy
poetry
Parables uh the
Epistles um and uh the gospels so those
were the six sections so you would pick
something from Matthew Martin Luke and
John you would pick a uh a parable
something from one of The Parables you
would pick yeah
um tiger say
hello this is what he
does if the door is left open he's
coming in so say hello to Tiger y all um
okay so y'all would choose six something
from history something from prophecy
something from the poetical books
something from the gospel something from
The Parables uh and then we would bring
it or we would we would have to free
freestyle and make all of them connect
and the reason that we do this exercise
is to
demonstrate what I call verse
genetics the idea that every text in the
Bible is related because all the verses
of the Bible
ultimately revolve around the same
theme Christ and him crucified right
Jesus said search the scriptures for in
them you think you have eternal life and
these are they which testify of me so if
all the scriptures testify of Jesus then
all the scriptures are
related you can grab a verse from
Revelation you can grab something from
you know from Genesis and these texts
are going to be related as I like to say
some texts are twins some texts are you
know siblings some texts some verses are
cousins some verses are distant cousins
some vers are distant distant distant
cous cousins but they all contain the
same
DNA why because they're all related to
The Plan of Salvation they're all
related to
Jesus so um what we're going to do
tonight to kind of jump back in and get
our feet wet again with uh with um uh
freestyle Wednesday is um we're going to
go into the the the cooking room the
recipe room and what we're going to do
is we're going to throw out a bunch of
ingredients right doesn't have to be you
know we're not going by the conect six
like has to be something from history
has to be something from poetry we're
not doing that just random as as random
as you want and we're going to take
those ingredients and we're going to
cook together so y'all are going to help
me and I'm going to help you all right
y'all good put one in the chat if you
are ready to
cook and I know there is a little
delay so I'm going to I'm going to wait
a few seconds put a one in the chat if
you are ready
to
cook and I hope y'all y'all know how to
cook hopefully y'all know how to cook
and if you don't know how to cook you're
going to learn how to cook you you're
going to learn how to cook all right so
here come the
ones um so here's what we're going to do
hopefully you got your Bibles out so
make sure oh wow there's a there's a a
30 second time lapse all
right okay um we'll we'll make it work
we'll make it work so um here's what
we're going to do guys we're going to go
ahead and I want you to start throwing
out some ingredients okay what do you
want to see in this recipe so right now
we're we're throwing out the ingredients
and
then and then we're going to make a
recipe so we might take a little bit
from this verse here you know you got to
kind of figure out okay what do we want
to take from this verse what do we want
to take from this Bible story um and and
how much we going to take from this
Bible story how we going to season it
how we going to put it together what
ingredients going first uh that's all
that we're going to do with this cooking
room with this recipe room so um all
right I'm beginning to see some verses
come in um and it doesn't have to be a
verse by the way it can be just a story
in general so uh I got my computer in
front of
me um and I got my es sword open so I'm
going to write this
down uh I'm going to write down what you
guys are are are putting into the into
the ingredients
list uh let's see
here all right so I see y'all putting in
comments in the chat so let's go with
uh
um Matthew
4 we going toite write this
down and y'all keep putting it in the
chat so um Matthew
4 all right let's
see let me scroll down here Matthew
4 John
3:16 Psalm
271 27 verse1
uh Romans 8 verse
28 Romans 8 verse
28 uh let's see let's see let's
see John 8 is that John 8
verse1 John 8
verse1 uh Romans 4
verse4 all right first
corini 14
14 34 and
35 all right we got the story of
Ruth um what is 2 Samuel 23:10 in fact
when you guys are uh putting up uh your
verses just kind of if you could say hey
this is what this verse is about um that
would be helpful um so 2
Samuel 23 verse 10 and uh hey Linda even
if you're new to this feel free to to
drop a a verse or uh a Bible story
something you want to see in the recipe
right in the ingredients
so let's go one at the well uh in John
um John 10 verse 5 Romans 8
verse1 John
10 verse 5 Romans 8 verse
one all right yes that is a cat and uh
he goes wherever I go he just won't
leave me
alone uh let's see Psalm 33
verse1 Psalm 133 verse
1 okay uh I think I think we're GNA
we're going to stop right here cuz right
now we got 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13
ingredients did I say that right one 2 3
4 5 6 78 nine 10 11 12 yep 14
ingredients 14 ingredients now these uh
are some powerful ingredients by the way
by the way Matthew 4 was that Matthew
44 cuz I just have Matthew 4 I just want
to make sure it's Matthew 4 and verse 4
all right so um Matthew 4 and verse four
here's what I'm going to do I'm going to
ask you all if you if you have your
Bibles open to just copy the verse and
put it in the chat okay copy the verse
and put it in the chat so if someone can
put in Matthew
4:4 Matthew 4 and verse
4 um and for those of you that are just
joining we are
we are freestyling tonight um and so
we're taking ingredients that is Bible
verses and we're going to connect all of
these verses so we don't even know what
we're going to study yet we don't know
how this is going to turn out we're
freestyling that's why we call it
freestyle Wednesday and y'all are going
to help me as we freestyle so yeah tiger
tiger
tiger move a little they think you're a
statue
okay he's watching the screen by the way
he's watching myself and him on the
screen and he loves to do this all right
so um hopefully the the the the Tiger in
the screen because that's his name is
not
distracting um but if he is I'll just
I'll make a move all right
so Matthew 4
ver4 uh if we can put that in the chat
Matthew 4:4 let's put John 3:16 in in
the chat as well let's put Psalm 27:1 in
the chat um let's see here here's what
we
using
okay so John 8:10 woman where are your
accusers all right uh Samuel 23 verse 2
Samuel 23:10
okay yeah that's when Samson uh uh his
sword he arose and smoked the
Philistines until his hand was
weary all right 2 Samuel
23:10 all right um
we got the woman at the
well we have uh Romans
8:28 that's all
things all things work
together
um Romans
4:4 are y'all good with are y'all good
with
tiger oh s 33:1 Psalm 133 ver1 how
pleasant all right so we're just uh
Romans 8 verse1 there is therefore now
no
condemnation all right uh John 10 verse
5 right we got John 3:16 and then Romans
8:28 all things work together um let's
do
um let's do uh Psalm 27
verse1 Psalm 27
verse1 and 1 Corinthians
14 verse 34 I think someone already put
that up there
actually 1 Corinthians
14 verse
34 no maybe it is not
up okay it is
up so let's
uh 1 Corinthians
14 and verse
oh man y'all are y'all are
really well we'll see we we're going to
see if we can connect 1 Corinthians
14:34 but y'all are y'all
are yeah y'all are trying to get
uh get deep tonight
okay all right so let's begin you guys
everybody ready did we get John 10
verse5 John chap 10 verse5 was that
posted the Lord is my salvation Psalm
27 all right and then
uh all right strangely they will not
follow but the sheep hear my voice or
yeah yeah let's see John
five all right I think we got everything
you guys Romans 4:4 Romans 4:4 I don't
know if I skipped that one or I missed
that one but if someone has that let's
just go ahead and post it and then we're
going to jump in Romans 4 and verse
4 um all right Romans 4 and verse 4 I'll
wait for that to be posted um so let's
begin y'all let's
begin let's
begin
with
h let's let's begin with man shall not
live by bread alone but by every word
that proceeds out of the mouth of
God all right y'all let's talk about it
uh what is the significance of Matthew
chapter 4 and
verse4 man shall not live by bread alone
but by every word that proceedeth out of
the mouth of God I'll wait for y'all to
comment I'm going to just uh y'all put
in
uh Romans 4:4
all right so Matthew 4:4 man shall not
live by bread alone but by every word
that proceeds out of the mouth of God
how do youall want to break this down
how are we going to how we going to uh
put this in the
pop um let's
say that uh it is absolutely crucial
to understand
that the word of God is the
foundation of man's life right
um the thing that sustains us is not
what we eat in terms of physical food
but the text is telling us that the word
of God
is
our it is our
safety it is our
life and the reason why is it our life
why is it our
safety why is it so important for us to
eat the word of God
are y'all
thinking the word of
God makes us strong doesn't
it it's our
weapon the word of God is our weapon
y'all hold on and give me a second here
uh uh I I'm I'm cooking hold on one
second one second
so the word of God is our
weapon yeah yeah yeah word of God is our
weapon and um I'm jumping somewhere
right now give me one second
here um
okay got it so the word of God is our
weapon it nourishes our soul what else
does the word of God
do it nourishes our soul it sustains
us it is our
weapon let's just focus on it being our
weapon for a moment our
defense it is the word of God like a
two-edged
sword what do y'all think the word of
God is like a two-edged
sword the word of
God as our weapon let's go with that as
our weapon for a moment the word of God
as our
weapon is given to us for our
defense yeah yeah when they are like
that it is part of the weapons of our
Warfare which are not carnal But Mighty
through God to the pulling down of
strongholds casting down imagination and
every High thing that exalted itself
against the knowledge of God so so
imagine with me if you will um imagine
with me if you will that let's say you
know you are uh uh in
the let's say you're in the midst of a
battle and your name
let's say happens to be Eleazar 2 Samuel
chapter uh chapter 23 uh where the Bible
speaks about after him was Eleazar the
son of Dodo the AO white one of the
three mighty men with David when they
defied the Philistines that were
gathered together to battle and the men
of Israel were gone away he arose and
smote the Philistines until his hand was
weary and his hand clave unto The Sword
and the Lord wrought a great victory
that day and the people returned after
him only to spoil let me ask you
something when the word of God is in
your hand does it give you the ability
to defeat principalities and Powers what
do y'all
think how many of you would like to have
Victory so powerful that the sword CL
the sword claves to your how many of you
would would would love the sword of God
to clave
to your
hand in a way so powerful that you
cannot let it
go how many of you would like to be like
that mighty man I said Samson earlier
I'm sorry about that I was thinking
about the Donkey Jaw uh but it is this
is Eleazar one of the Mighty Men of
David and the sword in his hand was so
powerful
man what a powerful object lesson to
us the reason why so many of us get beat
up in
life maybe it's
because we don't know how to use the
sword of
God
right when when that trial
comes
when when that battle comes when when
that uh principality and power
arises and we don't know how to use the
word of God this becomes a serious issue
guys there's a Time coming that the word
of God will literally be our
defense it is called the time of trouble
and only those Marco who will not let go
of the
sword that's what this Mighty Man was
doing
he would not let
go of the
sword he would not let go the sword how
powerful a thought that God is going to
have Mighty Men at the end of time who
are so nourished with the word of God
who are so full of the word of God that
it is like a weapon in their hand not a
weapon of Destruction but a
weapon of
protection when all the principalities
and powers are gathered against God's
people at the End of
Time the word of
God will be their
Ultimate
Weapon let me see what y'all are saying
in the
chat that's right the sword of the
spirit that's the armor of God the sword
of the spirit is the word
yeah think about the CH in the garden
who had the words that kept the sword
that kept Sin from coming into the
Garden of
Eden like Jacob not letting go of the
Lord I like that
Clint not letting go of the sword is
literally not letting go of the
word and we know who the word is the
word is
Jesus this is why John 3:16 the Bible
says for God so loved the world that he
gave his only begotten son that
whosoever believeth in him should not
perish but have everlasting life why
he's giving his son as the sword he's
given his son as the
Weaponry that will enable us to overcome
principalities and Powers isn't that
beautiful is isn't that
beautiful as we consider why God sends
his son into the
world it is because he knows that
without the his son without that
word without that
sword we are
defeated we are D we are destroyed
and so he loves us so much he says I'm
going to arm you I'm going to give you a
weapon that will pull down every
stronghold that will defeat every
principality and power I will give you
something that will overcome anything
that is thrown at
you yeah and and this is why beloved
this is why this is why
this is why we can
say with Psalm 27:1 the Lord is my light
and my salvation Whom Shall I Fear the
Lord is the strength of my life of whom
shall I be afraid oh man
woo yes yes yes Psalm 27 verse1 why am I
not afraid because God so loved me that
he
sent a sword didn't Jesus say think not
that I'm come to send peace but I came
to bring a
sword you don't have to be afraid Psalm
27:1 is saying
listen the Lord the word the
sword it's all interchangeable the Lord
is my light and my salvation Whom Shall
I Fear the Lord is the strength of my
life of whom shall I be afraid this
Mighty Man wasn't afraid of anybody why
because he had the word of God the sword
of God he had a sword in his hand and he
would not let that sword
go yeah yeah yeah we need to make sure
our hands are are pure and clean we need
to make sure that our hands are worthy
of holding the sword and of course we
know listen
listen I'm watching your comments I'm
watching your comments
I'm watching your comments I'm watching
I'm seeing if y'all are cooking with
me so let me pull up Romans
4:4 Romans 4
verse4 uh one of the ingredients Romans
chapter
4 and verse
4 and Romans 4:4 says now to him that
worketh is the reward not reckon of
Grace but of debt let me add verse five
in there but to him that worketh not but
believeth on him that justifi the UN the
ungodly his faith is counted for
righteousness so you might be thinking
that when I have the sword in my hand
the glory comes to
me yes brother yes brother
Tennessee we can have false swords being
wielded in the church false word being
wielded in the church which is
ultimately a false Christ being wielded
in the church so we got to make sure
that we're holding on to the right
sword and trust
me just as God doesn't want you to let
go of his sword Satan doesn't want you
to let go of his sword if that's the
sword you're
holding he wants that sword to cleave to
your
hand so let me jump back to this don't
don't get it
twisted that with the sword in your hand
it's you doing the
work because it's not you doing the
work it's it's
Christ in you it's not your work
it is the faith and the righteousness of
Christ in
you don't get happy and go man look at
all these you know look at all these
these these sins I'm slaying look at all
these GI by the way it in that example
you know following this example we're
not slaying people we're slaying
sins how many of you ever felt like
you've been you've been surrounded by
like just thousands and thousands of
sins just like these mighty men were
surrounded by thousands of of of enemies
how many of you feel like man
Lord my life is
so I have so
many sins that are coming at me all at
the same time there's no way I can
defeat these
sins remember Psalm
27:1 the Lord is my salvation Whom Shall
I
Fear and don't think it's up to
me to fight this
fight it's not your work Romans 4:4 and5
it's not your work it's Christ
working in
you are y'all with me so
far yes Cassie no longer I it's not I
but Christ in me that doeth the work
um think of it this
way it is not
you that saves
yourself yeah it is not
you that saves yourself it is not you
that redeems
yourself you you need someone to redeem
you you need someone who is close
someone who is a redeemer the Bible
calls redeemers the nearest of kin you
need
someone who is going to come and find
you how y'all
doing we can't will the sword by
ourselves we don't have power to fight
darkness by we are lost without the
sword we're
Outsiders so so we need someone who's
going to come and redeem us we need a
redeemer we need someone who is so close
to us we need someone that is like that
is like the nearest of kin
someone who's going to say I will redeem
you you are mine kind of like the story
of
Boaz yeah are y'all with
me remember it is a story of Boaz and
Ruth
that ends up
producing
David which brings the the the the
Mighty Man upon the
scene when you have that Ruth and Boaz
moment of redemption it will ultimately
lead to mighty men in your
life and when I say mighty men in your
life what I'm saying is that Mighty Man
Jesus Christ he is the might
man that says I'm going to Comm in
you and I'm going to wield that sword in
you are we cooking
y'all are we
cooking you almost think
man all this through a woman through
Ruth I thought women are supposed to be
silent I thought women are supposed to
stay in the in the background and not be
seen and not be
heard because beloved Ruth
remember is a
is a gentile
woman Boaz marries this woman which when
you look at this picture of Boaz as a
type of Christ and Ruth as a type of the
church yes yes
yes Jesus knows that at the End of Time
the church the woman is going to be
facing principalities and
Powers she's going to need a
sword she's going to need to know how to
fight she's going to need to know how to
how to how to say the Lord is my
salvation Whom Shall I
Fear but it's not really
her
fighting it's not really her that is
doing the work it is Christ in
her you
know
it's this Redemption of of of of
Ruth and Bo through
Boaz it kind of reminds me of the idea
that the church is full of
people that the Lord
has forgiven has
redeemed people whom whom Satan has has
brought and thrown down in front of in
front of the Lord and said this person
has sinned this person has caught in
adultery this person is caught stealing
this person's caught all the these
people are all
crooked and do you remember in John
chapter 8 do you remember in
John 8:
10 what Jesus did with that woman caught
in
adultery oh Marco I like that verse
blessed be the Lord my strength which
teacheth My Hands to War and my fingers
to fight I don't think that's a kjb
version it might be might be a slightly
different version but that's a powerful
verse right there that's a powerful
verse right
there the woman at the not the woman at
the World by the way
I I'll come back to that in a moment in
John 8:10 when Christ says to the woman
where are your accusers don't y'all love
don't you love the fact
that Jesus Boaz Boaz the Divine
Boaz
redeemed the spiritual
Ru mainly by doing just that
woman where are your accusers I forgive
you not only do I forgive you but
[Music]
woman
woman John
4 are you
thirsty let me give you the Water of
Life let me give you the Water of Life
listen Ruth spiritual woman I I have
come to forgive you of your
sins woman where are your accusers I
have
come to give you the Water of
Life John
4 I have come to Grant you the word
Matthew 4:4 because I am the
word I've come in essence not only to
forgive you but also to equip you to
fight the good fight of Faith with this
sword in your hand I want you to know
that it is not you that do it that does
the work but I'm I'm the one doing it in
you I am the one doing it in you and I
will fight in you and through
you I'm doing this because I so love the
world
see everybody on the church everybody in
the church has the same
experience we should have the same
experience therefore therefore it would
make sense let's see let's see hold on
one second
here uh it would make sense are y'all
cooking with
me it would make sense
it would make
sense for all of us to have the same
prayer the same praise behold how good
and how pleasant it is for Brethren to
dwell together in unity what is it
that's supposed to unify the church oh
we all had the same experience we were
that woman caught in adultery we were
that woman at the well we were that
roof please please please do not
think that Jesus is saying that women
have no place in Salvation that women
ought to just you know stay in the back
and no no no God is you he he uses the
woman as a symbol of his
church and tells us listen at the end of
time it is not a man that's going to be
wielding The Sword and crushing the head
of the serpent it's a woman
Satan brought sin into the world through
a
woman God will use a woman at the end of
time to destroy Satan and
sin the head of the serpent will be
bruised under the heel of the
church shortly
what is it that keeps us unified when we
remember that we all have the same past
we were all corrupt we were all crooked
we were all that woman caught in
adultery but lo and behold our divine
Boaz came and redeemed us and gave us
the Water of Life to drink and that and
then said I am going to equip you to
defend yourself your accusers will not
come after you like that anymore I will
defend you I will be in you I will grant
you the sword why because I so loved you
and my desire My Desire is to bring all
people together to be a part of that
woman so that Brethren can dwell
together in
unity
are
y'all cooking with
me there is their therefore now Romans
8:1 there is therefore now no
condemnation to them which are in Christ
Jesus and have Christ Jesus in them are
y'all catching
that we were that Gentile woman that
Ruth we were that Gentile woman under
condemnation but when Christ saw
us he so loved the
world not just the Jews he so loved the
world that the Divine Boaz came into the
world to redeem those that were lost in
the world to redeem those Gentiles I'm
going to give you I'm going to I'm going
to I'm going to repel Satan your accuser
woman and I'm going to give you the
Water of Life to drink from the well I
am the water and I am even the
well I'm going to equip you with my
sword you're going to be like a mighty
man except you're you're a
woman my church at the end of time will
be fighting off principalities and
Powers not because of their own strength
not because of their own work but it's I
that works in them it is I that that
will be working in
them and so when the Devil comes at you
you can say to two things there's no
condemnation you can know two things
there is no condemnation because I'm in
Christ Jesus and you can also know the
Lord is my salvation Whom Shall I
Fear know this
know
this know that if the word of God let me
go here let me go
here are y'all smelling that
Aroma yeah that smells
good that smells good
um know this if the word of
God is our
weapon which means we ought to follow
the word the voice of God I need you to
know and understand
this according to John chap 10:3 this is
our last ingredient by the way according
to John 10:3 the Bible says to him the
Porter openeth and the sheep hear his
voice and he cth his own Sheep by name
and leadth them out and when he putteth
forth his own sheep he goeth before them
and the Sheep follow him for they know
his voice why do they know his voice
because they know his word listen to
this this is the ingredient and a
stranger will they not follow but will
flee from him for they know not The
Voice or the word word of
strangers just
know that if God is trying to get you to
follow his voice his word his sword have
his sword in your hand the devil The
Stranger is trying to get you to follow
his voice his word his sword a sword of
persecution versus the Sword of the
spirit a false word versus the true word
a false Christ versus the true
Christ just know
this and if you know this if you know
that it is by the spirit that we hear
his voice then pray pray for that word
of the
spiritual pray that you understand the
love of God how much he so loved the
world how much he so loved the world
that
he
sent his word into the
world his word that would be be the very
sword in our
hand that he would give to us after
redeeming us our divine
Boaz so that we don't have to fear
because the Lord is our
Salvation we don't have to fear because
the Lord has said where are your
accusers we don't have to fear because
the Lord has said I'm going to give you
the water of life that you will never
thirst
again and when we know
this when we when we have that
confidence that it is Christ in us not
him that worketh but Christ in us his
righteousness his grace working through
us then
then we know
wow just as isn't that isn't God
something else Satan got into Satan
defeated the world through S uh through
a woman God's going to use a woman to
defeat Satan at the end of time isn't
God something else isn't God something
else so I can have the confidence
there is no condemnation when I'm in
Christ because he said to me where where
was that con that that that convict you
where are those that accuse
you yeah
yeah this is why beloved we ought to be
able to look around in our church and
say how pleasant it is for brothers and
sisters to dwell together why because we
all had the same story we all came out
of the same we all came out of of of
condemnation we were all given the Water
of Life now we are all truly brothers
and
sisters and now the last part of this
meal is to just let it
marinate you let it
cook you just put it on a stove you
cover it and then you just let the the
steam of the
spirit
just let it
cook let it cook and every now and then
you walk
by and you catch a whiff of that meal
and you're like oh
man yes yes
yes we've we've added the the salt and
the seasonings and we want to bring out
the flavor and the longer you let it sit
the better it comes when you digest it
the longer you meditate on this the
longer you you let it sit in the
heart man this is good
food this is good cooking you let it
simmer yes yes yes you let it
simmer and then you serve
it then you serve it take this out to
the
world try
this try this meal right
here tell me what you
think all right
y'all how was the food
tonight how was the food tonight how did
y'all enjoy cooking
tonight was it good
five in the
chat if if uh if we ate good
tonight
yeah that was a good
recipe y y'all gave some really good
ingredients in this
one yeah and so guys this is how you do
it this is part of what we do in photo
theology so I'm I'mma make a plug real
quick so for those of you who want to
learn how how to do this on a you know
we'll be doing this every every
Wednesday but in my photo theology
class um we go
into great
detail on how to use this principle to
study the Bible
better so um if you guys would like to
number one support power of the Land
Ministries number
two join in that photo theology class I
want you to go to in fact let me put it
in the chat uh you can just go to
um uh let me see here this is my patreon
page I'll put it in the link uh in the
description after the uh after this is
uh
uploaded but here it is power of the lab
so it's patreon
.cp powerthe land um look for you can
either look for the master class photo
theology master class or you can look
for for the for the excuse me for the
photo theology beginners class the three
Monon class okay uh and yes if you do
the Daniel and Revelation tier uh photo
theology is included
okay um all right so that's my plug but
but you
guys you can do this you can do this
what we just did tonight go through the
Bible and and just pick five verses
don't pre-think these verses you saw
what we did tonight pick five verses
okay I'm G choose this this this this
this and then throughout the day let
this be your daily exercise let me see
if I can connect these five ingredients
let me see what I can cook up with these
five ingredients with these 10
ingredients with these 20
ingredients
right start to practice this on your own
because ultimately you guys um the
reason I'm doing these freestyle
Wednesdays is for you to grasp the
importance of studying the word of God
for yourself
and starting to do it with
principles that will help you unpack the
word in a deeper and more meaningful
way all right
so that's it guys thank you for joining
uh joining uh freestyle Wednesday
tonight I will see you again next
Wednesday and we may have a guest with
us so just stay tuned but thank you
again guys may God bless you and may God
continue to sharpen the word of God in
your hand and to feed you with his word
amen amen